JOSHUA T. FISHER C++ C Python CMake Buildbot 16802 NE 104TH CT, REDMOND WA 570-239-4750 = j.fisher@digipen.edu = joshuatfisher.com

Objectives

Taking a project from source to installer is a fascinating process to me, and one I strive to improve in the projects I work on. In addition, I'm interested in learning more about better memory management patterns for C and C++ programmers. I've worked with the scripting language Zilch, developed by the Research and Development arm of DigiPen, and have worked with both binding it with C++ as well as having done minor work on expanding its standard library.

Experience

DigiPen Research and Development (Zero Engine) Internship - CI Maintenance • 4/2015 - Current

- Extending the functionality of our Buildbot CI system.
- Adding image difference testing to Zero Engine's CI routine.
- Added basic replay functionality to Zero Engine for CI testing.
- Adding program fork capability to the standard Zilch library.

Team Salt (7 Team Members) - Technical Director

- 4/2015 Current
- Extending the functionality of the core engine developed with The Adjective Noun.
- Writing and maintaining a new input (keyboard, mouse, gamepad) backend.

The Adjective Noun (4 Team Members) - Build Master/Engine Architect

- **8/2014 4/2015**
- Maintaining and extending our CMake build system.
- Creating and maintaining the "core" systems that allow our other programmers to develop derivative systems.
- Binding our engine to Zilch, a scripting language we use for some game play code.
- Creating gameplay components when needed.

Arby's - Cashier

11/18/2008 - 08/18/2013

Education

Digipen

Expected Completion: 04/2017 • Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

- Wrote a component based architecture for my second year game engine.
- Built a basic Fixed Block Size Memory Pool allocator for my Second semester game Soular Eclipse.

Activities

DigiPen Student Senate Member

• 10/2013 - Current

DigiPen Guest Lecture Committee Member

■ 1/2014 - Current